[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
A rat…
Are you dreaming?
There's a rat…
Talking in your sleep?
You've got that weird habit too.
You're the weird one.
You… you were awake?
Dreaming of your dad again?
Not him this time.
Then who?
You.
Me?
You haven't even seen my face.
So how'd you know it was me?
Because...
I know the way you smell.
Song Yi.
Xu Feiyu.
Get up!
Yong Qi.
You're up early.
Early my foot, look at the time.
Is Feiyu still asleep?
He… he's still asleep.
Hey.
Hey hey!
Song Yi.
Huh?
You're acting strange.
Strange how?
Not at all…
You two last night?
We slept great last night.
Out the second we laid down.
Slept like babies.
Really?
Really.
But then?
So I hear you tried
to sleep with Xu Feiyu?
He… he told you even that?
So no explanation for me?
Ugh.
I just wanted to try shock therapy.
Never thought it'd fail.
Sister Yun chewed me out for it.
Tsk.
Yong Qi
I heard the line of guys chasing you in college
stretched to Europe.
None of them did it for you?
You sure you're straight?
Hm?
What are you on about…
Hold on.
Song Yi.
Hm?
Don't tell me you're jealous over me?
I'm not.
Nonsense.
So I'm right?
Song Yi.
No way.
You're done for.
You're really done for.
I'm not, okay.
Stop pointing.
Oh.
Careful, careful.
Yong Qi
I'm hungry.
Look after him
I'm off.
He… he… he left?
You…
What were you two talking about?
Xu Feiyu.
How about you talk to me first
about me trying to sleep with you?
Um.
I…
That was…
probably…
me talking in my sleep last night…
I didn't know Song Yi was such a gossip.
And you're one to talk?
What's he done to you
these past few days?
Are you two close enough now
to be sharing secrets like that?
It's not exactly a secret.
No reason to hide it.
Huh?
Who exactly is hiding anything?
You...
What are you getting at?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Song Yi has no sense of boundaries.
Don't let him lead you astray.
He's the carer you hired for me.
You could've told me.
Huh?
Ugh.
Okay okay okay.
Breakfast is ready on the table.
Go on and eat.
Okay.
Eat with me.
No, I have to run to the shop.
You go ahead.
Mm.
All right then.
Song Yi.
Song Yi!
Yeah! I'm coming.
Walk me to the parking lot.
Sure thing.
What're you looking at with that look?
Ever since you showed up
I feel like Feiyu's become...
a different person.
That's not normal.
So what?
Is how he is now bad?
I don't know if this is good for him or bad.
Song Yi.
Do you really see Feiyu as a little brother?
I don't even know what you're saying...
Oh right.
Weren't you off to the shop?
Don't change the subject
I know exactly what you're thinking.
You two are already swapping clothes.
You come barging into his life
and if one day
he learns about you and Song Yang,
what then?
Come on that's enough
I know what I'm doing.
Go on hurry back.
Customers are waiting.
The obss lady's not there.
That's no good.
Go on, get going.
Go, go.
Hurry back.
Go.
Mm.
I've gotta say.
Yong Qi's cooking
is unbeatable.
Whatever she makes
comes out Michelin-level.
Fries.
Say ahh.
Ahh.
Tell me
when your eyes heal
what do you most want to do?
Would you…
want to do it with me?
Yeah.
I'll do it with you.
That's not an answer.
Doing it isn't the same as wanting to.
What's the difference?
Just say it.
What do you want to do?
There's tons of things.
Then tell me
the first one that pops into your head.
Mm…
Sunrise
I want to paint a sunrise from a mountaintop.
That's easy.
Sure, I'll take you.
Really?
Yeah
I want to see the sunrise too.
Then it's a promise.
No backing out!
Yeah.
It's a promise.
Say ahh.
Mmm.
Mm.
This.
What is this thing?
Sister Yun?
Weren't you coming back next week?
Why are you back early?
Any later
and the flowers wilt.
You're so sweet.
Come on
give me one of those mom hugs.
Come here.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Oh right
I got home and Xu Feiyu wasn't there
I thought he was here.
Oh.
Song Yi took him out to clear his head.
Don't worry, if they're together he's fine.
Seems that junior of yours isn't bad.
Don't get me started,
he's a handful too.
But this time those two
seem like two peas in a pod.
Whoo!
Oh sorry.
Hey?
That guy over there
did he come with you?
Introduce us.
He's… my little brother.
He's so hot,
just my type of puppy boy.
Puppy boy?
You've never seen him get mean.
Even a mastiff runs.
He bites.
Oooh~
I'm warning you don't go near him.
Hey!
Hey handsome
add me on WeChat?
He's my real little brother
so hands off.
Our house rule is no dating while young.
I don't mind.
It's just WeChat
I'm sure my "big brother"
wouldn't mind, would he?
Hmm
I see.
Hey, handsome.
What's with your eyes?
Blinded by my good looks.
Satisfied now?
Nothing to see, go dance.
All right, break it up.
Go on, go on, go on.
Quite the player, huh.
And I don't even have your WeChat.